<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Haax - Personal Blog</title>
    <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Haax - Personal Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://haax9.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OSINT/GEOINT - Investigating and geolocating #2 - Overpass Turbo</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/osint-geoint/osint-flight-volume2-overpassturbo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/osint-geoint/osint-flight-volume2-overpassturbo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;More than a year ago, I published a first post dedicated to the geolocation of a commercial flight from a photo taken in the plane and based on various research and open source tools. However, other tools exist and are, in my opinion, not enough covered in media. So I thought it would be interesting to write a few lines about them. And then, once again, like a running gag in our discussion groups, a photo also taken from a plane was sent to us. It turns out that this is a perfect case to introduce these tools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Geolocation of a flight from a photo? Let&amp;rsquo;s go for episode 2!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YogoshESD-CTF - CLUDEOSINT</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/osint-geoint/yogoshesd-ctf-cluedosint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/osint-geoint/yogoshesd-ctf-cluedosint/</guid>
      <description>[NO ENGLISH VERSION - Only French is available for this post]
Le challenge &amp;ldquo;CLUEDOSINT&amp;rdquo; a été joué dans le cadre du YogoshESD-CTF, un évènement en ligne proposé par l&amp;rsquo;école ESD en partenariat avec Yogosha et BZHack. Ce challenge a été spécialement créé par DocKali et Madame Https et consiste en un scénario de 15 challenges OSINT. Ce billet détaille l&amp;rsquo;investigation menée et la résolution des différents challenges. 
1/ Cognomen (10 points) Contexte: Vous êtes enquêteur privé.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YogoshESD-CTF - OSINT Challenges</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/osint-geoint/yogoshesd-ctf-osint-global/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/osint-geoint/yogoshesd-ctf-osint-global/</guid>
      <description>[NO ENGLISH VERSION - Only French is available for this post]
Le Yogosh-ESD CTF est un évènement en ligne proposé par l&amp;rsquo;école ESD en partenariat avec Yogosha et BZHack. Plusieurs catégories de challenges étaient présentes, comme pour la majorité des évènements de ce type. Arrivé 7e au classement, en m&amp;rsquo;étant notamment concentré sur les challenges OSINT, ce billet détaille les solutions de quelques un de ces challenges (hors challenge CLUEDOSINT qui a droit à un articlé dédié!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTF InterIUT 2020 - OSINT &amp; SE (aka the world worst phishing)</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/inter-iut-2020/osint_se_challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/inter-iut-2020/osint_se_challenge/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The CTF Inter IUT is an initiative started a few years ago by the ENSIBS school. Being online and open to all this year, we decided with a small group of friends to take a look at the different challenges. This post explains the solution of the challenge &amp;ldquo;La DGSE, c&amp;rsquo;est moi&amp;rdquo; on OSINT and Social Engineering topics.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSINT/GEOINT - Investigating and geolocating #1 - Commercial flight</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/osint-geoint/osint-flight-volume1-tracking-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/osint-geoint/osint-flight-volume1-tracking-challenge/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A few days ago, a good friend sent me a picture taken from a plane for an OSINT/GEOINT challenge. The goal was to find the flight departure, arrival, but also, where the picture was taken. The topic being rather fun and considering the variety of information and skills needed to solve the challenge, I thought it would be interesting to write about it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box - Remote</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/remote/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/remote/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Remote is an easy Windows machine. An open NFS share allows you to get sources for the websute and get the administrator password. User access is retrieved through a remote command execution on the &amp;ldquo;Umbraco&amp;rdquo; CMS. Privilege escalation exploits the &amp;ldquo;UsoSvc&amp;rdquo; service to spawn an administrator shell and get access.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box - Cascade</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/cascade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/cascade/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cascade is a Windows machine considered easy/medium. An anonymous RPC access allows domain users enumeration and an anonymous search through LDAP allows to get a password using one account attribute. Then, the enumeration of SMB shares and available files reveals a VNC configuration file, giving another password once decrypted. The target account is used as a service and it is possible to get the binary. A fast reverse engineering gives the password through decryption function. Privilege escalation is done using a particular account that is supposed to be deleted.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box - Sauna</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/sauna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/sauna/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sauna is a Windows machine considered easy and Active Directory oriented. The company&amp;rsquo;s website indicates a potential list of users, allowing to perform a brute force through an ASRepRoasting attack. Getting a shell through WinRM allow to list the domain properties and find a password in the WinLogon registry keys. This user has the necessary rights (DCSync) to dump the NTDS database, which allows to connect with the NTLM hash of the administrator.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box - Monteverde</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/monteverde/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/monteverde/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Monteverde is a Windows machine considered easy/medium and Active Directory oriented. An anonymous pseudo access allows to list domain accounts and help identifying a trivial account. The analysis of a network share allows to retrieve an account member of the &amp;ldquo;Azure Admins&amp;rdquo; group. Privilege escalation is performed through the exploitation of Azure AD Connect.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box - Nest</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/nest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/nest/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nest is a Windows machine considered easy/medium. An anonymous SMB access allows to retrieve a first non-privileged account. The recovery of an encrypted password and sources of a Visual Basic project allows lead the user&amp;rsquo;s password decryption. Privilege escalation is done through a &amp;ldquo;reporting&amp;rdquo; service allowing to get a new encrypted string on the disk. The decryption of this last one allows an administrator access.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box - Resolute</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/resolute/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/resolute/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Resolute is a Windows machine considered easy/medium and Active Directory oriented. An anonymous login allows you to list accounts in the domain and identify a default password. Obtaining a shell thtough WinRM allows then to list the domain properties and to find a password for a user member of the local &amp;ldquo;DnsAdmins&amp;rdquo; group. Privilege escalation is done through a DLL hijacking.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box - Forest</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/forest/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Forest is a Windows machine considered as easy/medium and Active Directory oriented. An anonymous access allows you to list domain accounts and identify a service account. This one is vulnerable to an ASREP Roasting attack, providing user access through WinRM. The privilege escalation is achieved through the exploitation of the &amp;ldquo;PrivExchange&amp;rdquo; vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NorzhCTF 2020 - OSINT - Familly Business</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/nozrhctf-2020/familly_business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/nozrhctf-2020/familly_business/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New year, new NorzhCTF edition, organized next to the FIC 2020. As I am no longer student at ENSIBS, I had the opportunity to participate in the event. This post deals with the solution of &amp;ldquo;Familly Business&amp;rdquo;, an OSINT/SOCMINT challenge divided in 2 parts.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box - Jarvis</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/jarvis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/jarvis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[NO ENGLISH VERSION - Only French is available for this post]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jarvis est une machine Linux catégorisée comme facile/moyenne. L&amp;rsquo;exploitation d&amp;rsquo;un injection SQL sur le site web permet de récupérer un accès limité. Une première phase d&amp;rsquo;escalade de privilège est réalisée grâce à une injection de commande dans un script. Enfin, la compromission de la machine peut être faite grâce à un binaire SUID (systemctl) en construisant un service.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box - Haystack</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/haystack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/hackthebox/haystack/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[NO ENGLISH VERSION - Only French is available for this post]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Haystack est une machine Linux catégorisée comme facile et plutôt intéressante, faisant intervenir ELK. L&amp;rsquo;énumération des endpoints web et des indices permet de récupérer un accès SSH utilisateur tandis que l&amp;rsquo;exploitation de la CVE-2018-17246 sur le composant Kibana permet de récupérer un accès plus intéressant. Enfin, l&amp;rsquo;exploitation d&amp;rsquo;un Logstash mal configuré permet d&amp;rsquo;élever ses privilèges.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NorzhCTF 2019 &amp; RedHackCTF 2019 - Windows AD - Game of Pwn</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/norzhctf-2019-redhack-2019/game-of-pwn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/norzhctf-2019-redhack-2019/game-of-pwn/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The NorzhCTF, organized in conjunction with the 2019 FIC, gave me the opportunity to create, in collaboration with &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/AzrakelK&#34; target=&#34;blank&#34;&gt;@AzrakelK (L0n3w0lf)&lt;/a&gt;, the attack scenario in relation to an Active Directory domain. This article gives details about this challenge and presents our solution. The challenge has been replayed during the RedHack CTF 2019 under the same name.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santhacklaus CTF 2018 - Solved Challenges</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/santhacklausctf-2018/santhacklaus-ctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/santhacklausctf-2018/santhacklaus-ctf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[NO ENGLISH VERSION - Only French is available for this post]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Le Santhacklaus CTF 2018 est un challenge Jeopardy en ligne, organisé par quatre étudiants de l&amp;rsquo;IMT Lille Douai &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/_nwodtuhs&#34; target=&#34;blank&#34;&gt;@_nwodtuhs&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/m3lsius&#34; target=&#34;blank&#34;&gt;@m3lsius&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/Ch3n4p4N&#34; target=&#34;blank&#34;&gt;@Ch3n4p4N&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/Th4cho&#34; target=&#34;blank&#34;&gt;@Deldel&lt;/a&gt;. Cet article traite des différents challenges que j&amp;rsquo;ai réussi et eu le temps de faire.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECW 2018 - Web - Intrusion (5 challenges)</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/ecw-2018/web-intrusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/ecw-2018/web-intrusion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ECW 2018 is a French Jeopardy challenge organized by the PEC (French Pôle d&amp;rsquo;Excellence Cyber) in partnership with the Bretagne county, Airbus and Thales.  Intrusion is a 4 (+1 extra) challenge based realist web scenario. It aims Ruby on Rails and cookie manipulation in order to become admin on the production website.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECW 2018 - Web - Troll.JSP</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/ecw-2018/web-troll-jsp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/ecw-2018/web-troll-jsp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ECW 2018 is a French Jeopardy challenge organized by the PEC (French Pôle d&amp;rsquo;Excellence Cyber) in partnership with the Bretagne county, Airbus and Thales. &amp;ldquo;Troll.JSP&amp;rdquo; is challenge based on the CVE-2017-5638 exploitation, executing code to change a session variable and then display the flag.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECW 2018 - Web - SysIA</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/ecw-2018/web-sysia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/ecw-2018/web-sysia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ECW 2018 is a French Jeopardy challenge organized by the PEC (French Pôle d&amp;rsquo;Excellence Cyber) in partnership with the Bretagne county, Airbus and Thales. SysIA is a challenge based on a LFI (Local File Inclusion) exploitation using the bash_history and the updatedb tool to find the flag.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 &amp; GPO - Hardening against personal data leak</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/articles/durcissement-windows-gpo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/articles/durcissement-windows-gpo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since the release of the Windows 10 operating system, many questions about user privacy have been raised. Indeed, even if our data were already collected before, Microsoft has opened their communication on the data collection with Windows 10. It allows mani people to open their eyes and become aware of things happenin.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web containers - Stop data sharing between websites</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/articles/web-containers-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/articles/web-containers-privacy/</guid>
      <description>If you regularly use an Internet browser and you know a little bit about Web technology, you generally know what data is retrieved by the different websites that you visit. If not, just know that each visited website stores information about you through different mechanisms (cookies in particular) which can for example identify you so you no longer have to enter your credentials.
However, this is only a small part of the data that publishers recover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Internet Box and Privacy - The iceberg summit</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/articles/internet-box-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/articles/internet-box-privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A little lighter post this time, dealing with connected internet boxes, and specifically the Miami Bboxes (which is a French ISP). Indeed, having one of these boxes, I wondered what I could find from a privacy point of view and what a basic and curious user could do with parameters. We will therefore see here that a certain number of default parameters are activated and that it is possible to act on them. I should point out that no box was mistreated in the context of these experiments : D.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best security practices for WordPress installations</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/articles/best-security-practice-wordpress-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/articles/best-security-practice-wordpress-installation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you want to set up your own website but you are not an expert, you may have seen the word &amp;ldquo;Wordpress&amp;rdquo; spread. It is a CMS (Content Management System) to help in the the creation of a website. Basically, it facilitates creation and management by providing a ready-to-use interface. Now all you have to do is customize your site and write your articles! No need to write code (even if it is possible to search and modify manually) !&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The password reuse threat</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/articles/password-reuse-threat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/articles/password-reuse-threat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;ve already heard it thousand times, but questions about passwords on Internet are more than ever critical for your privacy and personal data. Nowadays, Internet is used for (almost) everything and by (almost) everyone, from the simple cooking website to your bank account, through social networks, marketing websites or even your mailboxes. It makes a lot of websites, account, and so, passwords.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECW 2017 - Web - Path Through</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/ecw-2017/web-path-through/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/ecw-2017/web-path-through/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The ECW 2017 is a French Jeopardy challenge organized by the &amp;ldquo;Pôle d&amp;rsquo;Excellence Cyber&amp;rdquo; in partnership with the &amp;ldquo;Région Bretagne&amp;rdquo;, Airbus and Thalès. Path Through is a web challenge based on blind SQL Injection.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECW 2017 - Web - Hall of Fame</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/ecw-2017/web-hall-of-fame/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/ecw-2017/web-hall-of-fame/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The ECW 2017 is a French Jeopardy challenge organized by the “Pôle d’Excellence Cyber” in partnership with the “Région Bretagne”, Airbus and Thalès. Hall of Fame is a web challenge based on Union SQL Injection.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quaoar Virtual Machine - Walkthrough</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/vulnhub/quaoar-virtual-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/walkthroughs/vulnhub/quaoar-virtual-machine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Quaoar&amp;rdquo; is a &amp;ldquo;Boot2Root&amp;rdquo; VM originally created for the Hackfest 2016 CTF. It aims to train your computer security skills. You just have to launch the Virtual Machine, and then find a way to get root ! This VM is in free access on Vulnhub.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TamuCTF 2017 - Steganography - Musical Bits</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/tamuctf-2017/stegano-musical-bits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/tamuctf-2017/stegano-musical-bits/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The TamuCTF is a Jeopardy-style CTF. This walkthrough is explaining the &amp;ldquo;Musical Bits&amp;rdquo; challenge which is a Steganography challenge. &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/Haaxmax&#34; target=&#34;\_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;I&lt;/a&gt; worked with &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/ErwanFily&#34; target=&#34;\_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Iptior&lt;/a&gt; on this one and it tooks severals hours of pain before success! Let&amp;rsquo;s go!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conferences &amp; Talks</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/conferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/conferences/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rump Session Hack2G2 - Online Self Fingerprinting 101
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Talk [FR] : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ays3CL76NVA&#34;&gt;Youtube link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Slides [EN] : &lt;a href=&#34;https://haax.fr/docs/Rump_H2G2_Online_Self_Fingerprinting_101.pdf&#34;&gt;Rump_H2G2_Online_Self_Fingerprinting_101.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About haax.fr</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a personal website used to publish different things. You can find some CTF (Capture The Flag) write-ups, Virtual Machines walkthroughs or articles about privacy. It can be for people who knows a little bit the InfoSec field but, most of time, they will be for neophytes who want to learn things. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to write everyhting in both French and English (you can switch language in the sidebar panel).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
