<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Awareness on Haax - Personal Blog</title>
    <link>https://haaxmax.github.io/en/tags/awareness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Awareness on Haax - Personal Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://haaxmax.github.io/en/tags/awareness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Android Internet Box and Privacy - The iceberg summit</title>
      <link>https://haaxmax.github.io/en/articles/internet-box-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haaxmax.github.io/en/articles/internet-box-privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A little lighter post this time, dealing with connected internet boxes, and specifically the Miami Bboxes (which is a French ISP). Indeed, having one of these boxes, I wondered what I could find from a privacy point of view and what a basic and curious user could do with parameters. We will therefore see here that a certain number of default parameters are activated and that it is possible to act on them. I should point out that no box was mistreated in the context of these experiments : D.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best security practices for WordPress installations</title>
      <link>https://haaxmax.github.io/en/articles/best-security-practice-wordpress-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haaxmax.github.io/en/articles/best-security-practice-wordpress-installation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you want to set up your own website but you are not an expert, you may have seen the word &amp;ldquo;Wordpress&amp;rdquo; spread. It is a CMS (Content Management System) to help in the the creation of a website. Basically, it facilitates creation and management by providing a ready-to-use interface. Now all you have to do is customize your site and write your articles! No need to write code (even if it is possible to search and modify manually) !&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The password reuse threat</title>
      <link>https://haaxmax.github.io/en/articles/password-reuse-threat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haaxmax.github.io/en/articles/password-reuse-threat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;ve already heard it thousand times, but questions about passwords on Internet are more than ever critical for your privacy and personal data. Nowadays, Internet is used for (almost) everything and by (almost) everyone, from the simple cooking website to your bank account, through social networks, marketing websites or even your mailboxes. It makes a lot of websites, account, and so, passwords.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>