<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GEOINT on Haax - Personal Blog</title>
    <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/categories/geoint/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GEOINT on Haax - Personal Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://haax9.github.io/en/categories/geoint/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>OSINT/GEOINT - Investigating and geolocating #2 - Overpass Turbo</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/osint-geoint/osint-flight-volume2-overpassturbo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/osint-geoint/osint-flight-volume2-overpassturbo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;More than a year ago, I published a first post dedicated to the geolocation of a commercial flight from a photo taken in the plane and based on various research and open source tools. However, other tools exist and are, in my opinion, not enough covered in media. So I thought it would be interesting to write a few lines about them. And then, once again, like a running gag in our discussion groups, a photo also taken from a plane was sent to us. It turns out that this is a perfect case to introduce these tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Geolocation of a flight from a photo? Let&amp;rsquo;s go for episode 2!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YogoshESD-CTF - CLUDEOSINT</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/osint-geoint/yogoshesd-ctf-cluedosint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/osint-geoint/yogoshesd-ctf-cluedosint/</guid>
      <description>[NO ENGLISH VERSION - Only French is available for this post]
Le challenge &amp;ldquo;CLUEDOSINT&amp;rdquo; a été joué dans le cadre du YogoshESD-CTF, un évènement en ligne proposé par l&amp;rsquo;école ESD en partenariat avec Yogosha et BZHack. Ce challenge a été spécialement créé par DocKali et Madame Https et consiste en un scénario de 15 challenges OSINT. Ce billet détaille l&amp;rsquo;investigation menée et la résolution des différents challenges. 
1/ Cognomen (10 points) Contexte: Vous êtes enquêteur privé.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YogoshESD-CTF - OSINT Challenges</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/osint-geoint/yogoshesd-ctf-osint-global/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/osint-geoint/yogoshesd-ctf-osint-global/</guid>
      <description>[NO ENGLISH VERSION - Only French is available for this post]
Le Yogosh-ESD CTF est un évènement en ligne proposé par l&amp;rsquo;école ESD en partenariat avec Yogosha et BZHack. Plusieurs catégories de challenges étaient présentes, comme pour la majorité des évènements de ce type. Arrivé 7e au classement, en m&amp;rsquo;étant notamment concentré sur les challenges OSINT, ce billet détaille les solutions de quelques un de ces challenges (hors challenge CLUEDOSINT qui a droit à un articlé dédié!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSINT/GEOINT - Investigating and geolocating #1 - Commercial flight</title>
      <link>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/osint-geoint/osint-flight-volume1-tracking-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://haax9.github.io/en/writeups/osint-geoint/osint-flight-volume1-tracking-challenge/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A few days ago, a good friend sent me a picture taken from a plane for an OSINT/GEOINT challenge. The goal was to find the flight departure, arrival, but also, where the picture was taken. The topic being rather fun and considering the variety of information and skills needed to solve the challenge, I thought it would be interesting to write about it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>